Finding Aid for Penrod/Hiawatha Company postcard collection, 1950-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Penrod/Hiawatha Company postcard collection 1950-2014
Penrod/Hiawatha Company.
1.3 linear feet
8 postcard boxes over 5000 postcards
92456 Bb 2
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of John Penrod (Donor no. 7986 ) and first came to the library in 1991. Periodic additions have been received.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research; images may not be reproduced for commercial use. Academic researchers wishing to reproduce postcards must contact the Penrod/Hiawatha Company to obtain permission.
The Penrod/Hiawatha Company of Berrien Springs, Michigan, produces and distributes postcards and other photographic items for tourists. Photographer John Penrod (1930- ) founded the company in 1959 in Berrien Springs when he purchased a small postcard company in the city. Penrod gradually expanded his enterprise by purchasing competing postcard companies including the Hiawatha Card Company, A.E. Luce, L.L. Cook Company, Ludington News Company, Michigan Card Company, Pemble Brothers Wholesale, and Upper Michigan Press. In addition to postcards, Penrod/Hiawatha produces advertising, commercial, and tourist items, such as calendars, brochures, souvenir picture booklets, and business cards.
The Penrod/Hiawatha Company collection is mainly comprised of postcards, although some supplemental photographic items directed toward tourists is also included. The postcards, numbering more than 5,000, primarily are of the Michigan landscape and its towns and cities, covering every region of the state. Typical postcard themes dominate, particularly natural scenery, outdoor recreation, and shopping districts. The postcards date from the 1950s through the opening decades of the twenty-first century, although very few display copyright dates. The collection is divided into the following series.
Non-Postcard Items (calendars, brochures, booklets): Box 1
Non-Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards: Box 2
Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, 1970s-1990s: Boxes 2-5
Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, mid- to late 1990s: Boxes 5-6
Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, late 1990s-2000): Boxes 6-7
Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, 2001-2004: Box 8
Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, 2005-2014: Box 9
Oversize and miscellaneous: Box 10
As batches of postcards are received every years, it was decided to arrange the items in blocks of time according to the date of their accession. Thus for the researcher interested in a specific city, it will be necessary to examine the listing for each of the series.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ada (Mich.); Adrian (Mich.); Advertisements.; Albion (Calhoun County, Mich.); Algonac (Mich.); Allen Park (Mich.); Allendale (Mich.); Alma (Mich.); Aloha State Park (Mich.); Alpena (Mich.); Ann Arbor (Mich.); Arcadia (Mich.); Askel (Mich.); Athens (Mich.); Au Sable River (Mich.); Baldwin (Mich.); Battle Creek (Mich.); Bay City (Mich.); Bear Lake (Mich.); Beaver Island (Mich.); Bellaire (Mich.); Belle Isle (Detroit, Mich.); Benton Harbor (Mich.); Benzie State Park (Mich.); Benzonia (Mich.); Berrien Springs (Mich.); Bessemer (Mich.); Bete Grise (Mich.); Beulah (Mich.); Big Bay (Mich.); Big Rapids (Mich.); Birmingham (Mich.); Bloomfield Hills (Mich.); Bob-Lo Amusement Park (Ont.); Boyne City (Mich.); Brighton (Mich.); Brimley (Mich.); Brockway Mountain (Mich.); Buchanan (Mich.); Burt Lake State Park (Mich.); Cadillac (Mich.); Calumet (Mich.); Caro (Mich.); Cassopolis (Mich.); Cedar River (Mich.); Cedar Springs (Mich.); Cedarville (Mich.); Centreville (Mich.); Charlevoix (Mich.); Cheboygan (Mich.); Chelsea (Mich.); Christmas (Mich.); Clare (Mich.); Clinton (Lenawee County, Mich.); Coldwater (Mich.); Coloma (Mich.); Colon (Mich.); Copper Harbor (Mich.); Croton (Mich.); Crystal Falls (Mich.); Curtis (Mich.); De Tour Village (Mich.); Dearborn (Mich.); Decatur (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.); Dexter (Mich.); Dowagiac (Mich.); Drummond Island (Mich.); Dundee (Mich.); Durand (Mich.); Eagle Harbor (Mich.); East Lansing (Mich.); East Tawas (Mich.); Eaton Rapids (Mich.); Elk Rapids (Mich.); Eloise (Hospital: Wayne County, Mich.); Escanaba (Mich.); Fayette (Mich.); Flint (Mich.); Fort Wilkins (Mich.); Frankenmuth (Mich.); Frankfort (Mich.); Franklin (Mich.); Freeland (Mich.); Fremont (Mich.); Gaylord (Mich.); Gladstone (Mich.); Glen Arbor (Mich.); Glen Haven (Mich.); Glennie (Mich.); Good Hart (Mich.); Grand Haven (Mich.); Grand Marais (Mich.); Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grand Traverse Bay (Mich.); Grayling (Mich.); Greenville (Mich.); Grosse Pointe (Mich.); Gull Lake (Mich.); Gwinn (Mich.); Hamtramck (Mich.); Hancock (Mich.); Harbor Springs (Mich.); Hardy Dam (Mich.); Harper Woods (Mich.); Harrison (Mich.); Hartwick Pines State Park (Mich.); Hastings (Mich.); Hell (Mich.); Hessel (Mich.); Hiawatha National Forest (Mich.); Higgins Lake (Mich.); Highland Park (Mich.); Hillsdale (Mich.); Historic sites.; P.J. Hoffmaster State Park (Mich.); Holland (Mich.); Honor (Mich.); Houghton (Mich.); Houghton Lake (Mich.); Indian River (Mich.); Interlochen (Mich.); Interlochen State Park (Mich.); Ionia (Mich.); Irish Hills (Mich.); Iron Mountain (Mich.); Iron River (Mich.); Ironton (Mich.); Ironwood (Mich.); Ishpeming (Mich.); Isle Royale (Mich.); Jackson (Mich.); Kalamazoo (Mich.); Kalkaska (Mich.); Kewadin (Mich.); Lac La Belle (Mich.); Lake Ann (Mich.); Lake City (Mich.); Lake Leelanau (Mich.); L'Anse (Mich.); Lansing (Mich.); Leland (Mich.); Les Cheneaux Islands (Mich.); Lincoln Park (Mich.); Little Girl's Point (Mich.); Little Traverse Bay (Mich.); Livonia (Mich.); Lowell (Mich.); Ludington (Mich.); Ludington State Park (Mich.); Mackinac, Straits of (Mich.); Mackinac Bridge (Mich.); Mackinac Island (Mich.); Mackinac Island (Mich.); Mackinaw City (Mich.); Manistee (Mich.); Manistique (Mich.); Marinette (Wis.); Marion (Mich.); Marquette (Mich.); Mason (Mich.); Mears (Mich.); Menominee (Mich.); Mesick (Mich.); Midland (Mich.); Milford (Mich.); Mio (Mich.); Mitchell State Park (Mich.); Monroe (Mich.); Montague (Mich.); Mount Clemens (Mich.); Mount Pleasant (Mich.); Munising (Mich.); Muskegon (Mich.); Muskegon State Park (Mich.); Naubinway (Mich.); New Buffalo (Mich.); Newaygo (Mich.); Newberry (Mich.); Niles (Mich.); Northport (Mich.); Northville (Mich.); Old Mill Creek State Park (Mich.); Old Mission Point (Mich.); Omena (Mich.); Onekama (Mich.); Orchard Beach State Park (Mich.); Oscoda (Mich.); Otsego Lake State Park (Mich.); Owosso (Mich.); Paradise (Mich.); Paulding (Mich.); Paw Paw (Mich.); Penrod/Hiawatha Company.; Pentwater (Mich.); Peshawbestown (Mich.); Petoskey (Mich.); Petoskey State Park (Mich.); Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore (Mich.); Plymouth (Mich.); Pontiac (Mich.); Porcupine Mountains State Park (Mich.); Port Huron (Mich.); Prudenville (Mich.); Rapid River (Mich.); Reed City (Mich.); Rochester (Mich.); Rockford (Mich.); Rogers City (Mich.); Romulus (Mich.); Roscommon (Mich.); Roseville (Mich.); Royal Oak (Mich.); Saginaw (Mich.); Saint Clair (Mich.); Saint Ignace (Mich.); Saint Johns (Mich.); Saint Joseph (Mich.); Saugatuck (Mich.); Sault Sainte Marie (Mich.); Scottville (Mich.); Seney National Wildlife Refuge (Mich.); Silver Lake (Oceana County, Mich.); Sister Lakes (Mich.); Sleeping Bear Dunes National Lakeshore (Mich.); South Haven (Mich.); South Manitou Island (Mich.); Southfield (Mich.); Spring Lake (Mich.); Sterling Heights (Mich.); Stony Lake (Mich.); Sturgeon Point (Alcona County, Mich.); Sturgis (Mich.); Suttons Bay (Mich.); Upper Falls (Luce County, Mich.); Lower Falls (Chippewa County, Mich.); Tahquamenon River (Mich.); Tawas Bay (Mich.); Tawas Point State Park (Mich.); Taylor (Mich.); Tecumseh (Mich.); Three Rivers (Mich.); Torch Lake (Mich.); Tourism.; Traverse City (Mich.); Trenton (Mich.); Troy (Mich.); Union Pier (Mich.); Vandalia (Mich.); Wakefield (Mich.); Walloon Lake (Mich.); Warren (Mich.); Warren Dunes State Park (Mich.); West Branch (Mich.); Westland (Mich.); White Cloud (Mich.); Whitefish Point (Mich.); Whitehall (Mich.); Yankee Springs Recreation Area (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Contributors:
Penrod, John.
Genre Terms:
Calendars.; Postcards.; Souvenir viewbooks.
- Non-Postcard Items
  The Non-Postcard Items series contains brochures, booklets, and calendars produced by the Penrod/Hiawatha Company. The brochures are mainly advertisements for tourist attractions or services and are grouped alphabetically by city. The booklets focus on items of historical or scenic significance. The calendar collection contains several series of calendars dating from 1972. Each calendar usually has a different scenic theme.
  - Brochures and Booklets (Box 1)
  - Engagement calendars (Box 1)
- Non-Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards
  The Non-Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards series is comprised of postcards produced in the 1950s and 1960s by various companies that were eventually purchased by John Penrod. They are arranged alphabetically by city. General postcards of non-specific Michigan locations follow the city listing.
  - Cities
    - Adrian (Box 2)
    - Allen Park (Box 2)
    - Alpena (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 2)
    - Bay City (Box 2)
    - Benton Harbor (Box 2)
    - Berrien Springs (Box 2)
    - Big Bay (Box 2)
    - Birmingham (Box 2)
    - Bloomfield (Box 2)
    - Brighton (Box 2)
    - Calumet (Box 2)
    - Cedar River (Box 2)
    - Cedarville (Box 2)
    - Cheboygan (Box 2)
    - Christmas (Box 2)
    - Clare (Box 2)
    - Clinton (Box 2)
    - Crystal Falls (Box 2)
    - Curtis (Box 2)
    - Dearborn (Box 2)
    - Detroit (Box 2)
    - Belle Isle and Bob-Lo Island (Box 2)
    - Buildings and Sites (Box 2)
    - Churches and Universities (Box 2)
    - Downtown (Box 2)
    - Transportation (Box 2)
    - Dexter (Box 2)
    - Dowagiac (Box 2)
    - Drummond Island (Box 2)
    - Dundee (Box 2)
    - East Tawas (Box 2)
    - Eloise (Box 2)
    - Escanaba (Box 2)
    - Fayette (Box 2)
    - Flint (Box 2)
    - Gaylord (Box 2)
    - Gladstone (Box 2)
    - Grand Marais (Box 2)
    - Grayling (Box 2)
    - Grosse Pointe (Box 2)
    - Hamtramck (Box 2)
    - Hancock (Box 2)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 2)
    - Harper Woods (Box 2)
    - Harrison (Box 2)
    - Hazensisle Resort, Houghton Lake (Box 2)
    - Hell (Box 2)
    - Hessel (Box 2)
    - Highland Park (Box 2)
    - Houghton (Box 2)
    - Indian River (Box 2)
    - Irish Hills (Box 2)
    - Iron Mountain (Box 2)
    - Iron River (Box 2)
    - Jackson (Box 2)
    - Lincoln Park (Box 2)
    - Livonia (Box 2)
    - Landing (Box 2)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 2)
    - Manistique (Box 2)
    - Marquette (Box 2)
    - Midland (Box 2)
    - Milford (Box 2)
    - Mio (Box 2)
    - Monroe (Box 2)
    - Mt. Clemens (Box 2)
    - Munising (Box 2)
    - Naubinway (Box 2)
    - Newberry (Box 2)
    - Niles (Box 2)
    - Northville (Box 2)
    - Oscoda (Box 2)
    - Plymouth (Box 2)
    - Pontiac (Box 2)
    - Port Huron (Box 2)
    - Prudenville (Box 2)
    - Rochester (Box 2)
    - Rogers City (Box 2)
    - Roscommon (Box 2)
    - Roseville (Box 2)
    - Royal Oak (Box 2)
    - Saginaw (Box 2)
    - St. Clair (Box 2)
    - St. Ignace (Box 2)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 2)
    - Southfield (Box 2)
    - Sterling Heights (Box 2)
    - Taylor (Box 2)
    - Tecumseh (Box 2)
    - Trenton (Box 2)
    - Troy (Box 2)
    - Warren (Box 2)
    - West Branch (Box 2)
    - Westland (Box 2)
    - Ypsilanti (Box 2)
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards 1970s-mid 1990s
  The Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards series contain postcards produced in the 1970s up to the mid-1990s after Penrod purchased the Hiawatha Card Company The series was received as part of 1991-1995 accessions. The series is primarily arranged alphabetically by city. It also includes general postcards of non-specific Michigan locations and topics following the listing by city.
  - General
    - Commercial (Box 2)
    - Attractions / Museums (Box 2)
    - Churches (Box 2)
    - Corporations (Box 2)
    - Resorts (Box 2)
    - Restaurants (Box 2)
    - Shops (Box 2)
    - Historical Postcards (Box 2)
    - Lakes (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - Cities
    - Adrian (Box 3)
    - Albion (Box 3)
    - Algonac (Box 3)
    - Alma (Box 3)
    - Alpena (Box 3)
    - Andrews (Box 3)
    - Ann Arbor (University of Michigan) (Box 3)
    - Baldwin (Box 3)
    - Battle Creek (Box 3)
    - Bay City (Box 3)
    - Beaver Island (Box 3)
    - Benton Harbor (Box 3)
    - Bessemer (Box 3)
    - Big Rapids (Box 3)
    - Birmingham (Box 3)
    - Bloomfield Hills (Box 3)
    - Boyne (Box 3)
    - Buchanan (Box 3)
    - Cadillac (Box 3)
    - Calumet (Box 3)
    - Caro (Box 3)
    - Cassopolis (Box 3)
    - Cedarville (Box 3)
    - Charlevoix (Box 3)
    - Cheboygan (Box 3)
    - Coldwater (Box 3)
    - Colon (Box 3)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 3)
    - Dearborn (Box 3)
    - Detroit (Box 3)
    - Detour (Box 3)
    - Eagle Harbor (Box 3)
    - Elk Rapids (Box 3)
    - Empire (Box 3)
    - Fayette (Box 3)
    - Flint (Box 3)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 3)
    - Gaylord (Box 3)
    - Gladstone (Box 3)
    - Glennie (Box 3)
    - Grand Haven (Box 3)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 3)
    - Grayling (Box 3)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 3)
    - Hastings (Box 3)
    - Hillsdale (Box 3)
    - Holland (Hope College) (Box 3)
    - Houghton / Hancock (Box 3)
    - Iona (Box 3)
    - Iron City (Box 3)
    - Iron Mountain (Box 3)
    - Ironwood (Box 3)
    - Isle Royale (Box 3)
    - Ishpeming (Box 3)
    - Jackson (Box 3)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 4)
    - Langley (Box 4)
    - Lansing (Michigan State University) (Box 4)
    - Leelanau / Leland (Box 4)
    - Lowell (Box 4)
    - Ludington (Box 4)
    - Mackinac Bridge (Box 4)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 4)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 4)
    - Manistee (Box 4)
    - Manistique (Box 4)
    - Marion (Box 4)
    - Marquette (Box 4)
    - Mason (Box 4)
    - Menominee (Box 4)
    - Midland (Box 4)
    - Montague (see Whitehall) (Box 4)
    - Mount Pleasant (Box 4)
    - Musing (Box 4)
    - Muskegon (Box 4)
    - Naubinway (Box 4)
    - Newaygo (Box 4)
    - Niles (Box 4)
    - Northport (Box 4)
    - Owosso (Box 4)
    - Paw Paw (Box 4)
    - Pentwater (Box 4)
    - Petoskey (Box 4)
    - Pontiac (Box 4)
    - Port Huron (Box 4)
    - Reed City (Box 4)
    - Rockford (Box 4)
    - Roscommon (Box 4)
    - Rogers City (Box 4)
    - Saginaw (Box 4)
    - Saugatuck (Box 4)
    - South Haven (Box 4)
    - St. Johns (Box 4)
    - St. Joseph (Box 4)
    - Sturgis (Box 4)
    - Sutton's Bay (Box 4)
    - Tawas Bay (Box 4)
    - Three Rivers (Box 4)
    - Traverse City (Box 4)
    - Troy (Box 4)
    - Union Pier (Box 5)
    - Wakefield (Box 5)
    - Whitehall / Montague (Box 5)
    - Ypsilanti (Eastern Michigan University) (Box 5)
  - General
    - Lakes
      - Lake of the Clouds (Box 5)
      - Spring Lake (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Parks
      - Fort Wilkins (Box 5)
      - Higgins (Box 5)
      - Pictured Rocks (Box 5)
      - Porcupine (Box 5)
      - Silver Lake (Box 5)
      - Sleeping Bean National Park and Glen Lake (Box 5)
      - Warren Dunes (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Regions
      - Soo Locks (Box 5)
      - Tahquamenon Region (Box 5)
      - Thumb Area (Box 5)
      - Upper Peninsula (Box 5)
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards mid 1990s-late 1990s
  The Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, ca. 1993-1998 series contain postcards produced in the mid to late 1990s which were received by the library in 1996 and 1998 accessions. The series is primarily arranged first by general postcards of non-specific Michigan locations and topics. This is followed by the listing by city.
  - General
    - Animals and Birds (Box 5)
    - Botanical (Box 5)
    - Humor (Box 5)
    - Lakes I (includes Burt, Gull, Elk, Long, Houghton, Higgins, Otsego, Torch, Glen, White, Crystal, Paw Paw, Charlevoix, Walloon) (Box 5)
    - Lakes II (includes Huron, Michigan, Silver Lake, Sister Lakes, Superior) (Box 5)
    - Lighthouses (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous (includes campsites, flag, maps, state gem, state stone) (Box 5)
    - Native Americans (Box 5)
    - Non-Michigan (includes Chicago, Ohio, Indiana) (Box 5)
    - Parks, National (Box 5)
    - Parks, State (Box 5)
    - Rivers (Box 5)
    - Seasons (Box 5)
    - Sports (Box 5)
    - Sunsets and Shorelines (Box 5)
  - Cities
    - Ann Arbor (University of Michigan) (Box 5)
    - Askel (Box 5)
    - Baldwin (Box 5)
    - Battle Creek (Box 5)
    - Bellaire (Box 5)
    - Benton Harbor (see St. Joseph) (Box 5)
    - Benzonia (Box 5)
    - Berne (Box 5)
    - Beulah (Box 5)
    - Berrien Springs (Andrews University) (Box 5)
    - Bete Grese (Box 5)
    - Cadillac (Box 5)
    - Calumet (Box 5)
    - Cedar Spring (Box 5)
    - Cedarville (Box 5)
    - Charlevoix (Box 5)
    - Clinton (Box 5)
    - Coldwater (Box 5)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 5)
    - Crystal Falls (Box 5)
    - Curtis (Box 5)
    - Dearborn (Greenfield Village) (Box 5)
    - Detroit (Box 5)
    - Detour (Box 6)
    - Elk Rapids (Box 6)
    - Empire (Box 6)
    - Escanaba (Box 6)
    - Evansville (Box 6)
    - Fayette (Box 6)
    - Flint (Box 6)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 6)
    - Frankfort (Box 6)
    - Gaylord (Box 6)
    - Good Hart (Box 6)
    - Grand Haven (Box 6)
    - Grand Marais (Box 6)
    - Grand Rapids (Gerald Ford Museum, Frederick Meijer Gardens) (Box 6)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 6)
    - Harrison (Box 6)
    - Hessel (Box 6)
    - Holland (Box 6)
    - Houghton / Hancock (Michigan Tech University) (Box 6)
    - Indian River (Box 6)
    - Interlochen (Box 6)
    - Ironwood (Box 6)
    - Jackson (Jackson Prison) (Box 6)
    - Kalamazoo (Western Michigan University) (Box 6)
    - Lake City (Box 6)
    - Lansing (Michigan State University) (Box 6)
    - Leland (Box 6)
    - Ludington (Box 6)
    - Mackinac Bridge (Box 6)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 6)
    - Manistee (Box 6)
    - Manistique (Box 6)
    - Marquette (Box 6)
    - Menominee (Box 6)
    - Midland (Dow Gardens) (Box 6)
    - Muskegon (Box 6)
    - Northport (Box 6)
    - Oscoda (Box 6)
    - Paw Paw (Box 6)
    - Pentwater (Box 6)
    - Petoskey (Box 6)
    - Port Huron (Box 6)
    - Saginaw (Box 6)
    - Saugatuck (Box 6)
    - Soo Locks and Ships (Box 6)
    - South Haven (Box 6)
    - St. Joseph / Benton Harbor (Box 6)
    - Sutton's Bay (Box 6)
    - Tawas City (Box 6)
    - Traverse City (Box 6)
    - Whitehall (Box 6)
    - Ypsilanti (Box 6)
  - Regions
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 6)
  - Non-Michigan
    - Chicago (Box 6)
    - Ohio (Box 6)
    - Indiana (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards, late 1990s-2000
  The Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards series contain postcards produced in the late 1990s to 2000 and was received as part of a 2000 accession. The series is primarily arranged first by general postcards of non-specific Michigan locations and topics. This is followed by the listing by city.
  - General
    - Animals and Birds (Box 6)
    - Botanical (Box 6)
    - Humor' (Box 6)
    - Lakes I (includes Long, Higgins, Torch, Walloon) (Box 6)
    - Lakes II (includes Huron, Michigan, Silver Lake, Superior and Dunes) (Box 6)
    - Lighthouses (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous (includes collages, flags, maps, agates, state stone) (Box 6)
    - Parks, National (Box 6)
    - Parks, State (see also Lighthouses) (Box 6)
    - Rivers (Box 6)
    - Seasons (Box 6)
    - Sports (Box 6)
    - Sunsets and Shorelines (Box 6)
  - Cities
    - Ada (Box 6)
    - Ann Arbor (University of Michigan) (Box 6)
    - Arcadia (Box 6)
    - Bay City (Box 6)
    - Bay Harbor (Box 6)
    - Battle Creek (Box 6)
    - Benton Harbor (see also St. Joseph) (Box 6)
    - Berrien Springs (Andrews University) (Box 6)
    - Beulah (Box 6)
    - Beulah City (Box 6)
    - Boyne City (Box 6)
    - Calumet (Box 6)
    - Charlevoix (Box 6)
    - Christmas (Box 6)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 6)
    - Douglas (Box 6)
    - Eagle Harbor (Box 6)
    - Eagle River (Box 6)
    - East Lansing (Michigan State University) (Box 6)
    - East Tawas (Box 6)
    - Edwardsburg (Box 6)
    - Elk Rapids (Box 6)
    - Empire (Box 6)
    - Escanaba (Box 6)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 6)
    - Frankfort (Box 6)
    - Gaylord (Box 7)
    - Glen Lake (Box 7)
    - Grand Haven (Box 7)
    - Grand Marais (Box 7)
    - Grand Rapids (Gerald Ford Museum. John Bull Park Zoo) (Box 7)
    - Grayling (Box 7)
    - Harbor springs (Box 7)
    - Higgins Lake (Box 7)
    - Holland (Box 7)
    - Houghton / Hancock (Box 7)
    - Indian River (Box 7)
    - Interlochen (Box 7)
    - Jackson (Box 7)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 7)
    - Kalkaska (Box 7)
    - Lansing (Box 7)
    - Leland (Box 7)
    - Ludington (Box 7)
    - Mackinac Bridge (Box 7)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 7)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 7)
    - Manistee (Box 7)
    - Manistique (Box 7)
    - Marquette (Box 7)
    - Marshall (Box 7)
    - Mason (Box 7)
    - Menominee' (Box 7)
    - Midland (Dow Gardens) (Box 7)
    - Munising (Box 7)
    - Muskegon (Box 7)
    - Niles (Box 7)
    - Northport (Box 7)
    - Onekama (Box 7)
    - Pentwater (Box 7)
    - Petoskey (Box 7)
    - Pigeon (Box 7)
    - Point Betsie (Box 7)
    - Port Huron (Box 7)
    - Reed City (Box 7)
    - Saginaw (Box 7)
    - Saugatuck (Box 7)
    - Soo Locks and Ships (Box 7)
    - South Haven (Box 7)
    - St. Ignace (Box 7)
    - St. Joseph/ Benton Harbor (Box 7)
    - Suttons Bay (Box 7)
    - Traverse City (Box 7)
    - Wakefield (Box 7)
    - Whitefish Point (Box 7)
    - Whitehall-Montagne (Box 7)
    - Ypsilanti (Box 7)
  - Regions
    - Les Cheneaux Islands (Box 7)
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 7)
- Penrod / Hiawatha Postcards 2001-2004
  The Penrod/Hiawatha Postcards, ca. 2001-2004 series contain postcards produced approximately 2001-2004. The series is primarily arranged first by general postcards of non-specific Michigan locations and topics. This is followed by the listing by city.
  - General
    - Amish (Box 8)
    - Animals (Box 8)
    - Attractions / Museums (Box 8)
    - Bridges, Tridges (Box 8)
    - Churches (Box 8)
    - Humor (Box 8)
    - Resorts (Box 8)
    - Seasons (Box 8)
    - Ships (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Cities
    - Alpena (Box 8)
    - Ann Arbor (University of Michigan) (Box 8)
    - Baldwin (Box 8)
    - Battle Creek (Box 8)
    - Beulah (Box 8)
    - Charlevoix (Box 8)
    - Cheboygan (Box 8)
    - Christmas (Box 8)
    - Copper Harbor (Box 8)
    - Detroit (Box 8)
    - East Tawas (Box 8)
    - Empire (Box 8)
    - Escanaba (Box 8)
    - Frankenmuth (Box 8)
    - Grand Haven (Box 8)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 8)
    - Harbor Springs (Box 8)
    - Holland (Hope College) (Box 8)
    - Houghton / Hancock (Box 8)
    - Ithaca (Box 8)
    - Jackson (Box 8)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 8)
    - Lansing (Michigan State University) (Box 8)
    - Ludington (Box 8)
    - Mackinac Bridge (Box 8)
    - Mackinac Island (Box 8)
    - Mackinaw City (Box 8)
    - Manistee (Box 8)
    - Manistique (Box 8)
    - Marquette (Northern Michigan University) (Box 8)
    - Menominee (Box 8)
    - Midland (Box 8)
    - Muskegon (Box 8)
    - Nahma (Box 8)
    - New Buffalo (Box 8)
    - Pentwater (Box 8)
    - Petoskey (Box 8)
    - Port Huron (Box 8)
    - Saugatuck (Box 8)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 8)
    - South Haven (Box 8)
    - St. Ignace (Box 8)
    - St. Joseph (Box 8)
    - Traverse City (Box 8)
  - Lakes, Lighthouses, Parks, etc.
    - Lakes
      - Crystal Lake (Box 8)
      - Higgins Lake (Box 8)
      - Houghton Lake (Box 8)
      - Lake of the Clouds (Box 8)
      - Torch Lake (Box 8)
      - Walloon Lake (Box 8)
      - Great Lakes (Box 8)
    - Lighthouses
      - Au Sable Point (Box 8)
      - Bete Grise (Box 8)
      - Big Sable Point (Box 8)
      - Cheboygan (Box 8)
      - Copper Harbor (Box 8)
      - Crisp Point (Box 8)
      - Eagle Harbor (Box 8)
      - Fort Gratiot (Box 8)
      - Forty Mile Point (Box 8)
      - Frankfort (Box 8)
      - Grand Island East Channel (Box 8)